<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- This file is part of the DITA Open Toolkit project hosted on 
     Sourceforge.net. See the accompanying license.txt file for 
     applicable licenses.-->
<!-- (C) Copyright IBM Corporation 2001, 2005. All Rights Reserved.
 *-->
<!DOCTYPE concept
  PUBLIC '-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN'
  'dtd1.2/technicalContent/dtd/concept.dtd'>

<concept id="sample_concept" xml:lang="en-US">
  <title>Introduction to Northampton Concervation Area Signs</title>
  <shortdesc>A brief description of the official wooden signs for marking Northampton conservation areas.</shortdesc>
  <conbody>
    <p>The Northampton conservation areas has wooden signs to help hikers know what area they are on. The signs are wooden boards
         with grooved letters usually mounted on two wooden posts. In some cases, the signs are mounted on trail fenses. Commons 
         features on signs include grooved letters that are wear-resistant and circular indentations for logo plates representing
         sponsoring organizations.</p>
    <p>As of January 2019, the signs have had two major versions. The very first version used pressure-treated boards
       usually painted in red. After about a decade of wear-and-tear, the paint on many of the signs started to peel, and some
       of the pressure-treated lumber started to rot.</p>
    <p>To reduce future maintenance costs, the planning office started replacing severely damaged version one signs with version
         two signs made of locust boards with more durable absorbent finish on them.</p>
    <p>Version one and version two signs has two choices of hardware for mounting them onto posts. 
         The simpler and more common choice involves drilling holes directly through the sign face to mount the sign onto supporting ports
         using stainless nuts and bolts. While simple, this choice is not very aesthetically pleaning and can interfere with the placement
         of letters and logo plates.</>
    <p>The more complex choice of hardware uses two metal brackets that are bent at both ends.
  </conbody>
</concept>
